<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="assets/xml/rss.xsl" media="all"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Demo Site</title><link>https://example.com/</link><description>This is a demo site for Nikola.</description><atom:link href="https://example.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"></atom:link><language>en</language><copyright>Contents © 2021 &lt;a href="mailto:joe@demo.site"&gt;Your Name&lt;/a&gt; </copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 13:26:23 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>Nikola (getnikola.com)</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Beginning with Pytorch and remote sensing data</title><link>https://example.com/posts/beginning-with-pytorch-and-remote-sensing-data/</link><dc:creator>Your Name</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;English version below!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Olá pessoal&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eu estou envolvido em um projeto que utiliza Pytorch e dados de sensoriamento remoto. Eu tenho alguma familiaridade com aprendizado de máquina, e fiz meu mestrado utilizando algoritmos genéticos, mas esse é meu primeiro contato sério com redes neurais e o mundo de 'deep learning' e redes convolucionais.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Meu plano é postar sobre o meu progresso, para me ajudar a manter o ritmo e criar um compromisso público. Eu também espero que os textos possam ajudar outros.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Eu vou começar com a documentação oficial do Pytorch, e em particular o 'learn the basics' &amp;lt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://pytorch.org/tutorials/beginner/basics/intro.html"&gt;https://pytorch.org/tutorials/beginner/basics/intro.html&lt;/a&gt;&amp;gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Abraços
Roberto&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hi folks&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am involved in a project that requires Pytorch and remote sensing data. I am familiar with machine learning, and I did my master's using genetic algorithms, but this is my first serious contact with neural networks and the all world of deep learning and convolutional neural networks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am planning to post my progress to help me keep pace and have some public accountability. I also hope these posts can be helpful to others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will start with Pytorch's documentation, in particular the learn the basics &amp;lt;&lt;a class="reference external" href="https://pytorch.org/tutorials/beginner/basics/intro.html"&gt;https://pytorch.org/tutorials/beginner/basics/intro.html&lt;/a&gt;&amp;gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers
Roberto&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;

</description><guid>https://example.com/posts/beginning-with-pytorch-and-remote-sensing-data/</guid><pubDate>Fri, 19 Nov 2021 13:09:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Couch to 5k - I am back :)</title><link>https://example.com/posts/couch-to-5k-i-am-back/</link><dc:creator>Your Name</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday I restarted the Couch to 5k program. I completed the program a few years ago (before being a father), and even ran a few 5k and 10k runs. My top event was the Robin Hood half marathon in 2015. Well, since then, I haven't done much exercise, but once in a while, when I go for a short run, I immediately remember how much I like the post-run side effects. It is good for my body, and it is super good for my mental health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So, that is it - I wanted to share that I back, and hopefully I will keep going. This also seems a good theme to start the blog.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This week I will be swamped attending the Health Data Research UK summer school! I went last year to St Andrew's, and it seems a long time ago when we used to meet people face to face. But, I am happy with the online version; otherwise, it is unlikely I would be able to attend this year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Cheers, and see you around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;

</description><guid>https://example.com/posts/couch-to-5k-i-am-back/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>About me</title><link>https://example.com/posts/about-me/</link><dc:creator>Your Name</dc:creator><description>&lt;div&gt;&lt;p&gt;I work for the University of Nottingham as a team lead of research software engineers and data scientists.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have mixed professional experience, working as a software developer after my degree in Mathematics. A few years later, I returned to academia to pursue a master’s in Computer Science, followed by a PhD in Geography at Nottingham. Having worked a couple of years as a research fellow, mainly doing software development, I immediately took the opportunity to join the Digital Research Service as a Research Software Engineer. In the last couple of years, I have been working more with Health Data, the Tissue Directory and Coordination Centre, and the BBRMI-ERIC, a European research infrastructure for biobanking.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/body&gt;&lt;/html&gt;

</description><guid>https://example.com/posts/about-me/</guid><pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2020 20:21:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>